{
    "subject": "resource/Shooting_at_the_1900_Summer_Olympics_\u2013_Men's_300_metre_free_rifle,_standing",
    "predicate": "ontology/bronzeMedalist",
    "object": "resource/Charles_Paumier_du_Verger",
    "human_readable": "Charles Paumier du Verger won the bronze medal in Men's 300 metre free rifle, standing at the 1900 Summer Olympics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9874074459075928,
            "question": "Who won the bronze medal in Men's 300 metre free rifle, standing at the 1900 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9749676585197449,
            "question": "What was Charles Paumier du Verger's position in the Men's 300 metre free rifle, standing competition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.962531328201294,
            "question": "Was Charles Paumier du Verger a participant in the 1900 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9569700360298157,
            "question": "What event did Charles Paumier du Verger compete in at the 1900 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9547029137611389,
            "question": "In what year did Charles Paumier du Verger win a bronze medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9479770064353943,
            "question": "At which Summer Olympics did Charles Paumier du Verger win his medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7406646609306335,
            "question": "Which country did Charles Paumier du Verger represent at the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6391511559486389,
            "question": "What color medal did Charles Paumier du Verger receive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5164452791213989,
            "question": "What was the name of the athlete who won the bronze medal in this event?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0524488240480423,
            "question": "What type of shooting event was the competition?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles Paumier du Verger won the bronze medal in Men's 300 metre free rifle, standing at the 1900 Summer Olympics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_374_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the athlete who won the bronze medal in this event?",
            "html": "dbpedia_374_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What color medal did Charles Paumier du Verger receive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_374_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country did Charles Paumier du Verger represent at the Olympics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_374_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_374_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_374_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_374_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_374_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_374_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_374_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_374_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_374_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_374_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_374_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text mentions that Charles Paumier du Verger won a bronze medal in the **military rifle standing event** at the 1900 Summer Olympics, not the \"300 metre free rifle, standing\" event. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query is about evaluating whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"Charles Paumier du Verger won the bronze medal in Men's 300 meter free rifle, standing at the 1900 Summer Olympics.\"\n\nHere is the evaluation result in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_374/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt mentions that Charles Paumier du Verger won a bronze medal in the military rifle standing event at the 1900 Summer Olympics, which is consistent with the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information mentions that Charles Paumier du Verger participated in the Shooting event at the 1900 Summer Olympics in Paris and won a bronze medal in the military rifle standing event, which aligns with the statement that he won the bronze medal in Men's 300 metre free rifle, standing at the 1900 Summer Olympics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Charles Paumier du Verger won a bronze medal in the military rifle standing event at the 1900 Summer Olympics, not the 300 metre free rifle, standing.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}